风暴就要来了 而你们两个 你们就摇逸在风暴的中心
Storm's coming. And you boys, you are smack in the middle of it.
你的孩子 你的萨姆 还有其他的孩子
You know the truth about Sammy and the other children.
- 安迪·格立科特 - 艾娃·威尔森
- Andrew Gallagher. - Ava Wilson.
- 我谁也没有伤害 - 还没有
- I didn't hurt anybody. - Not yet.
麦克斯 你的能力从 7个月前开始的 对吗？
Max, your abilities started seven months ago, right?
- 你怎么知道 - 我们的母亲死于同一场事故
- How'd you know that? - The same thing killed our mothers.
你和我都是被选中的 为什么
You and I were chosen.For what?
我不知道
I don't know.
在事情发生前 我看到这个家伙死了
I saw this guy die, days before it happened.
你可以控制人们做事 不是吗？你可以控制他们去想些什么
You can make people do things. You can tell them what to think.
- 很棒的车 我能开下吗 - 当然 伙计
- Cherry ride. Can I have it? - Sure, man.
你肯定是我们中的一份子 什么？ 超能力者
You must be one of us. The psychics.
滚吧 伙计
Screw you, buddy,
因为我是从帕奥利亚来的秘书 我不属于任何东西的一部分
because I'm a secretary from Peoria and I'm not part of anything.
恶魔告诉我 他们有他们的战士 会在即将到来的战争中战斗
This demon tells me they have soldiers to fight in this coming war.
超能力者为恶魔战斗
Psychics fighting on hell's side.
那黄眼的男人让我去做 一些事 恶心的事
The yellow-eyed man tells me to do things, awful things.
- 他告诉我他 有一个大计划 - 也许这就是他的计划
- He told me he's got big plans. - Maybe this is his plan.
- 也许我们都该是… - 什么 杀手 得了吧
- Maybe we're all supposed to be… - What? Killers? Give me a break.
没有人有艾娃的任何消息 她消失了 知道吗
No one's heard anything about Ava. She just into thin air, you know.
- 硫磺 - 艾娃
- It's sulfur. - Ava.
魔鬼来过这里
The demon's been here.
如果坏事将要发生 它会来的很快 他们那边拥有所有的底牌
There's something big and bad coming. Their side holds all the cards.
我们无法躲避 你也不可能保护我
You can't run from this. And you can't protect me.
可恶 萨姆 整件事正逐渐失去控制
Damn it, Sam, this whole thing is spinning out of control.
嗨 这次别忘了多加点洋葱
Don't forget the extra onions this time, huh?
伙计
Dude…
我应该是那个 吃着双份洋葱… 开车的人
I'm the one who's gonna have to ride in the car with your extra onions.
嗨 看看他们有没有馅饼卖
Hey, see if they got any pie.
给我带点馅饼
Bring me some pie.
I love me some pie.
萨姆？
Sam?
硫磺
Sulfur.
萨姆
Sam.
Sammy?
萨姆
Sam?
Sammy.
萨姆
Sam!
[邪恶力量 第2季第21集]
安迪？
Andy?
萨姆？
Sam.
- 你在这儿干嘛？- 我不知道那
- What are you doing here? - I don't know.
我在这儿干嘛？
What am I doing here?
- 我不知道 - 我们在哪儿？
- I don't know. - Just…Where are we?
- 安迪 听着 冷静下来 - 我冷静不下来
- Andy, look, calm down. - I can't calm down.
我刚从个怪异的梦中醒来
I have just woke up in frigging Frontierland.
你记得的最后一件事是什么？
What's the last thing you remember?
说实话
Honestly?
抽我第四根大麻
My fourth bong-load.
很奇怪
It was weird.
突然之间 有一种非常剧烈的味道 就像是…
All of a sudden, there was this really intense smell, like, uh-
- 像硫磺？- 你怎么知道？
- Like sulfur? - How did you know that?
- 迪恩 - 你兄弟他… 他在这儿吗？
- Dean. - Your brother, is he here?
我不知道他在哪儿
I don't know where he is.
我不知道他是否…
I don't know if he's-
救我 我被锁在这了
Help me, please. I'm locked in here.
有人吗？
Hello?
不 救救我
Help. Help me.
好了 好了 我在这儿 我们救你出去 好吗？
Okay. Okay. I'm here. We're gonna get you out, all right?
- 等一下 - 拜托
- Just hold on a second. Please.
- 好了 马上 - 拜托
- All right, one second. - Please.
- 艾娃 - 我的上帝 萨姆
- Ava? - Oh, my God. Sam.
- 我猜你俩互相认识 - 是的
- I guess you know each other. - Yeah.
你怎么… 我怎么…
How did you…? I mean…
- 艾娃 你一直都在那里面吗？- 什么一直？
- Ava, have you been here this whole time? - What whole time?
- 我半小时前在里面刚醒 - 你已经消失5个月了
- I just woke up in there a half an hour ago. - Well, you've been gone for five months.
我和我兄弟到处找你
My brother and I have been looking for you everywhere.
这不可能 因为我在2天前刚见过你
Okay, that's impossible, because I saw you two days ago.
你没有 对不起
You didn't. I'm sorry.
但这没有道理 这… 不…
But that makes no sense. It's…
我的上帝
Oh, my God.
我的未婚夫 布洛迪 如果我失踪那么久 他肯定会抓狂的
My fiancé, Brady, if I've been missing for that long, he must be freaking out.
好吧
Well
嘿
Hey.
安迪 也同样抓狂了
Andy. Also freaking out.
好的 发生了什么？
Okay. What's happening?
我… 我真的不清楚
I don't know. I don't really know yet.
但我知道一件事 我知道我们三个人的共通点
But I know one thing. I know what the three of us have in common.
你好 有人吗
Hello? Is anybody there?
- 也许不只3个 - 等等
- Maybe more than three. - Wait.
有人吗？
Hello?
嗨
Hey.
- 嗨 你们没事吧？- 我想是吧
- Hey, are you guys all right? - I think so.
我叫萨姆
I'm Sam.
- 我是扎克 - 莉莉
- I'm Jake. - Lily.
- 还有没有其他人 - 没有了
- Are there any more of you? - No.
我们怎么会到这里来的？一分钟前我还在圣地亚哥
How did we even get here? A minute ago I was in San Diego.
如果能让你感觉好一点的话… 昨晚我还睡在阿富汗
Well, if it makes you feel any better, I went to sleep last night in Afghanistan.
让我大胆的猜下 你们俩都是23岁？
Let me take a wild guess. You two are both 23?
我们都是23岁 我们都有「能力」
We all are. And we all have abilities.
- 什么 - 始于1年多前
- What? - It started a little over a year ago…
你发现你可以做那些 你从前认为不可能的事
when you found you could do things. Things you didn't think were possible.
我有幻觉 我可以看到还没发生的事情
I have visions. I see things before they happen.
是的 我也是
Yeah, me too.
我可以把意志灌输到人们的脑中 像让他们做事
I can put thoughts into people's heads, like, make them do stuff.
不过别担心 我认为不会对你们起作用
But don't worry, I don't think it works on you guys.
但是听听这个 我一直在练习…
Oh, but get this, um, I've been practicing.
训练我的大脑 像冥想一样 好吗？
Training my brain, like meditation, right?
所以现在 我不只可以传输意志
So now, it's not just thoughts I can beam out but images too.
同样还有图像 像… 我想到的任何东西 就像… 哗 人们就看到了
Like, anything I want. It's like, bam! People, they see it.
我认识一个家伙 绝对的混蛋
This one guy I know, total dick.
我在他身上使用
I used it on him.
和同性恋做爱了一整天
Gay porn, all hours of the day.
就像是… 你们应该看看他的表情
It's just like-You should have seen the look on his face.
噢 好吧
Oh, okay.
那么如果你说「西蒙说把你 的钱包给我」 他们就会做？
So you go, "Simon says give me your wallet, " and they do?
你有幻觉？ 那很棒 我非常想要那样的能力
You have visions? That's great. I'd kill for something like that.
- 莉莉 听着 没事的 - 不 不是
- Lily, listen. It's okay. - No, it's not.
我碰到人
I touch people…
人的心脏就会停止
their hearts stop.
我几乎不能离开我的房子
I can barely leave my house.
我的生活也根本没有好转
My life's not exactly improved.
所以滚你的吧
So screw you.
- 我只想回家 - 我们不想吗？
- I just wanna go home. - And what, we don't?
- 别那样和我说话 - 嗨 伙计们 拜托
- Don't talk to me like that. - Hey gus please come.
听着 无论我们喜不喜欢 我们都在这里了
Look, whether we like it or not, we're all here.
所以我们都要面对这个
And so we all have to deal with this.
谁把我们带到这里？
Who brought us here?
并不该是「谁」 更应该是「什么」
It's less of a who. It's more of a what.
那是什么意思？
What does that mean?
是 呃…
It's, uh-
是一个魔鬼
It's a demon.
就是这个了
This is it.
上个月所有 出现恶魔征兆和预示的地方
All demonic signs and omens over the past month.
- 你开玩笑吗 这什么都没有 - 完全正确
- You're joking, there's nothing here. - Exactly.
拜托 一定会有什么的 那正常的呢 低等级的那些
Come on. There's gotta be something. What about the normal, low-level stuff?
- 你知道的 驱魔招魂那种 - 我告诉你了 什么都没有
- Exorcisms, that kind of thing. - That's what I'm telling you. Nothing.
完完全全的安静
It's completely quiet.
那我们怎么找萨姆 闭上眼睛点地图吗？
How we supposed to look for Sam? Close our eyes and point?
阿什 有什么线索吗？
Ash, what do you got?
好了 听着 没有什么关于萨姆的线索
Okay, listen, it's a big negatory on Sam.
拜托 伙计 你得给我们些线索
Come on, you gotta give us something.
我们正在这儿对着 3000多英里长的干草堆发呆呢
We're looking at a 3000-mile haystack here.
听着 迪恩
Listen, Dean…
我的确找到了一些线索
I did find something.
好吧 是什么
Well, what?
我不能在电话里说 迪恩
I can't talk over this line, Dean.
- 行了 我没有时间 - 找时间
- Come on, I don't have time for this. - Make time.
好吗？ 因为…
Okay, because this-
你好？ 有什么事？
What's up? What's going on?
不只是这事 基本一定会帮助你找到你弟弟的 这只是…
Not only does this almost definitely help you find your brother, this is…
太惊人了
It's huge.
所以到这儿来 马上
So get here. Now.
我想我们要去路边旅馆了 来吧
I guess we're going to the Roadhouse. Come on.
那么说我们是启示录中提到的 恶魔战争中的士兵？
So we're soldiers in a demon war to bring on the Apocalypse?
如果你要那样想的话…
When you put it like that.
- 我们是被挑选出来的 - 是的
- And we've been picked? - Yes.
- 为什么是我们- 我不确定
- Why us? - I'm not sure.
- 好吧 但是你瞧 我知道… - 萨姆
- Okay, but look, I just know…Sam.
对不起 通灵和特异功能是一回事 但是恶魔？
I'm sorry, psychics and spoon bending is one thing. But demons?
听着 我知道这听起来很疯狂
look I know it sounds crazy.
- 并不仅仅是听起来疯狂 - 我不关心你怎么想的 好吗？
- It doesn't just sound it. - I really don't care what you think.
但是如果我们被聚在一起了 就意味着开始了 那么我们…
If we're all gathered here that means it's starting. We gotta-
我唯一要做的就是 远离白痴 好吗？
The only thing I gotta do is stay away from wack jobs, okay?
我听够了 我要自己走了
I've heard enough. I'm better off on my own.
对你们来说 最好也一样
FYI, so are you.
扎克 等等
Jake. Hold on.
扎克
Jake.
有人吗？
Hello?
没事的 别害怕
It's all right. Don't be scared.
你迷路了吗？
Are you lost?
有人吗？
Hello?
回去
Get back.
这样你们知道了…
Just so you know?
那就是个魔鬼
That was a demon.
那个东西？我不确定 但是我想是只阿奇雷鬼
That thing, I'm not sure, but I think it was an Acheri.
一种把自己伪装成小女孩的魔鬼
A demon that disguises itself as a little girl.
还是没表明我们在哪里
Still doesn't tell us where we are.
- 安迪 你要不要和我一起 - 给我一分钟
- Andy, are you with me or what? - Give me a minute.
我还在考虑「魔鬼是真实的」 这个问题
I'm still working through "demons are real."
我从前见过那座钟
I've seen that bell before.
我想我知道我们现在在哪里了
I think I know where we are now.
冷橡木 南达科他州
Cold Oak, South Dakota.
这个镇子太闹鬼 以至于所有居民都逃离了
A town so haunted, every single resident fled.
太棒了 很高兴知道我们在 一个如此著名的地方
Swell. Good to know we're somewhere so historical.
为什么那个魔鬼 无论是什么把我们带到这里？
Why in the world would that demon or whatever put us here?
我也在疑惑这个问题
I'm wondering the same thing.
知道吗？ 这无所谓
You know what? It doesn't matter.
唯一该做的理智的事情 就是离开这该死的地方
Clearly, the only sane thing to do here is get the hell out of Dodge.
等等 等一下 莉莉 唯一离开这里的路 是穿过厚厚的丛林
Wait, hold on. Lily, the only way out's through miles of woods.
总比跟魔鬼在一起好
Beats hanging out with demons.
莉莉 听着 我们还不知道到底发生了什么
Lily, look, we don't know what's going on yet.
我是说 我们甚至都不知道 这里有多少魔鬼
We don't even know how many of them are out there right now.
- 是的 他是对的 我们应该… - 不要说「我们」
- Yeah, he's right. We should just…Don't say we.
我不是「我们」中的一部分 我和你们中任何一个 都没有共通点
I'm not part of we. I have nothing in common with any of you.
- 好了 听着 听着 我知道… - 你什么都不知道
- Okay, look, look, I know that… - You don't know anything.
我碰…
I…
我意外的碰到了我的女朋友
I accidentally touched my girlfriend.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
无论怎样
Whatever.
我感觉我是在一个噩梦之中 而且噩梦变的越来越坏
I feel like I'm in a nightmare and it just keeps getting worse and worse.
我也失去了亲人
I've lost people too.
就在外面 我有一个哥哥
I have a brother out there right now. I…
据我所知 他可能已经死了
He could be dead for all I know.
我们都处于不好的形势之中
We're all in bad shape.
但是我要告诉你 最好的解决问题的办法 就是团结在一起
But I'm telling you, the best way out of this is to stick together.
好吧
Fine.
我们要找铁 银和盐 任何的武器
We're looking for iron, silver, salt, any kind of weapon.
- 盐是种武器 - 这是个全新的世界
- Salt is a weapon? - It's a brave new world.
希望你的世界里面有食物 因为我他妈的饿死了
Well, hopefully there's food in your world because I'm frigging starving.
见鬼的
What the hell?
我的上帝啊
My God.
你看到艾伦了吗？
You see Ellen?
没有
No.
也没看到阿什
No Ash either.
哦 阿什 见鬼
Oh, Ash. Damn it.
嗨 你没事吧？
Hey. You all right?
没事 我只是…
Yeah. I'm just-
我不知道 有点头晕
I don't know, a little dizzy.
你… 你确定不是某种… 什么 某种奇怪的幻象？
- Are you sure it's not some kind of…What? Some kind of freaky vision thing?
不 更像是会为一个三明治 被折磨死了
No. More like, I'd kill for a sandwich.
我滴水未进已经有…
I haven't eaten since-
谁知道呢
Well, who knows.
不 这… 别担心 我没事 除了接连发生的这些事以外
No, it's-Don't worry. I'm fine, except for every thing that's happening.
伙计们 我找到了些东西
You guys? I found something.
- 盐 - 这太好了 安迪
- Salt. That's great, Andy.
现在我们都…
Now we all-
莉莉在哪儿？
Where's Lily?
莉莉？
Lily?
莉莉
Lily!
哦 我的上帝啊
Oh, my God.
好了 那
Okay, that's-
是真正的…
That's officially-
萨姆 她死了 她死了
Sam, she's dead, she's dead.
你说过我们因为 某种原因被挑选上了 那不是被挑选
You said we were chosen for a reason. That is not chosen. That's…
那是被杀
killed.
好了 知道嘛 我们得离开这里
Okay, yup. We have to get out of here.
- 我赞成这种心情 - 但并不确定那是种选择
- Yeah, I second that emotion. - Not sure that's an option.
- 什么- 莉莉试图离开
- What? - Lily was trying to leave.
恶魔不会让我们 这么容易就离开
The demon's not gonna let us get away that easy.
我们得准备好防御 下一次袭击
We gotta gear up for the next attack.
- 准备好？- 是的
- Oh. Gear up? - Yeah.
好吧 我不是士兵 我做不来
Okay, well, I'm not a soldier. I can't do that.
听着 如果你想活下来 你就得去做
Look, if you wanna stay alive, you're gonna have to.
我们走吧
Let's go.
好吧 我把她放下来
I'll get her down.
你知道吗… 我刚刚在想迪恩现在 能帮上多少忙
You know, I'm just thinking about how much Dean would help right now.
给我一部好用的电话
I'd give my arm for a working phone.
知道吗 你也许不需要电话
You know, you may not need one.
我… 呃 我是说 我以前从来没试过远距离的
I, uh-I mean, I've never tried it long distance before.
你身上有迪恩的什么东西吗 比如他碰过的东西？
But do you have anything of Dean's on you? Like something he touched?
- 我有张收据 这有用吗 - 是的
- I got a-I got a receipt. Will that work? - Yeah.
D·哈塞尔霍夫
"D·Hasselhoff?"
是的 那是迪恩的签名 这…
Yeah. That's Dean's signature. It-
这很难解释
It's hard to explain.
好吧
All right.
这…
This is-
阿什到底知道什么？
What the hell did Ash know?
我们根本没法知道艾伦在哪儿 或者她是否还活着
We got no way of knowing where Ellen is or if she's even alive.
我们也不知道阿什 到底想告诉我们什么 我们怎么才能找到萨姆？
We got no clue what Ash was gonna tell us. Now how the hell are we gonna find Sam?
我们会找到他的
We'll find him.
- 迪恩 - 不
- Dean? - No.
怎么回事？
What was that?
我不知道 头疼？
I don't know. Headache.
你经常这样头疼？
You get headaches like that a lot?
不
No.
一定是压力造成的
Must be the stress.
我肯定我看到什么东西
I could have swore I saw something.
什么意思 像… 像幻象 像萨姆那种的
What do you mean, like-Like a vision? Like what Sam gets?
- 什么 不 - 我只是问问
- What? No. - I'm just saying.
拜托 我不是那种通灵的
Come on, I'm not some psychic.
迪恩
Dean?
Dean.
迪恩？
Dean?
你能听到我吗？
Are you with me?
是的 我想是的
Yeah, I think so.
我看到了萨姆
I saw Sam.
我看到他了 鲍比
I saw him, Bobby.
那是种幻象
It was a vision.
我不知道为何
I don't know how.
但是… 没错
But, yeah. Hoo.
这就和掉进天堂一样有趣
That was about as fun as getting kicked in the jewels.
你还看到了什么？
What else did you see?
- 有一座钟 - 什么样的钟？
- There was a bell. - What kind of bell?
呃… 像一个大…
Uh, like a big bell with…
一座上面有某种雕刻的大钟 我不知道
some kind of engraving on it, I don't know.
- 雕刻？- 是的
- Engraving? - Yeah.
是一棵树吗 就像 一棵橡树？
Was it a tree? Like an oak tree?
是的 完全正确
Yeah. Exactly.
我知道萨姆在哪儿了
I know where Sam is.
我… 我不是什么超人 不是什么重要的事
I'm-I'm not Superman or anything. It's no big deal.
- 之前你在阿富汗 - 我开始是头疼
- You were in Afghanistan when this started? - Yeah, I started getting headaches.
然后 呃…
And then, uh…
发生了一次事故 有个伙计在一条破路上翻了车
there was this accident. This guy flipped his vehicle on a bad road.
被卡在下面
He got pinned underneath.
我像抬空气一样 把车从他身上抬起来
I lifted it off him like it was nothing.
大家都说这是 肾上腺素分泌异常
Everybody said it was a fluke adrenaline thing.
- 但是后来你又做了一次 对吗 - 800磅的台式压床
- But then you did it again, right? - Bench pressed 800 pounds…
轻而易举
stone-cold calm.
当然了 我从来没告诉过任何人 这太疯狂了
I never told anybody, of course. It's just too crazy.
是的 疯狂是相对的
Yeah, but crazy's relative.
我开始理解了
I'm starting to get that.
是的
Yeah.
顺便说一下 我 呃… 谢谢你所做的事
By the way, I, uh-I appreciate what you're doing here.
- 我做了什么 - 保持冷静
- What am I doing? - Keeping calm.
让大家保持冷静
Keeping them calm.
尤其是当想到自己是多么的古怪
Especially considering how freaked to hell you really are.
我之前一度非常垂头丧气 我知道是什么样子的
I've been in some deep crap before myself. I know the look.
想知道真相吗？
You wanna know the truth?
我有个哥哥 对吧？他一直都告诉我他会如何保护我
I got this brother, right? He's always telling me how he's gonna watch out for me…
一切都会没事的 就像我告诉他们的那样
how everything's gonna be okay, kind of like I'm telling them.
是吗
Yeah?
这次我不知道我还会不会相信
I don't know if I believe it this time.
我是说 这次所面对的东西的能力…
I mean, the size of what's coming.
比任何人所见过的都强
It's bigger than anyone's ever seen.
我是说 这将会很糟
I mean, it's gonna get bad.
我… 我不知道能否…
And I-I don't know if-
我们是否能挺过去
If we're gonna make it?
我们是否相信不重要
Doesn't matter if we believe it.
他们相信才重要
Only matters that they do.
我的占卜说我当初 不应该醒过来
My horoscope said I shouldn't have gotten out of bed.
你怎么样？
How you doing?
- 坚持的住吗 - 我还好
- Holding up? - I'm okay.
你呢？
What about you?
不太好
Not so okay.
为什么是我们 萨姆？
Why us, Sam?
我们做了什么遭受这个？
What did we do to deserve this?
我猜只是幸运
Just lucky I guess.
如果不是坏运气的话 也不应该一点运气都没有
Wasn't for bad luck, wouldn't have no luck at all.
迫不及待希望这能结束 那样我就可以装作 从来都没有发生过
I just can't wait for this all to be over so I can just pretend it never happened.
只想蜷缩在布雷迪的怀里 看深夜节目
I just want to curl up with Brady and watch bad TV.
怎么了
What is it?
萨姆
Sam.
你是不是…
Do you…
知道什么我不知道的事？
know something that I don't?
听着 艾娃
Look, Ava. I-
- 我很抱歉 我希望不必告诉你这些 - 告诉我什么
- I'm sorry, I wish I didn't have to tell you. - Tell me what?
当恶魔…
When the demon…
闯到你家带走你的时候…
broke into your house to take you…
你的未婚夫没能活下来
your fiancé didn't make it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
不 这…
No, it's-
扎克 你后面
Jake. Behind you.
你好啊 萨姆
Howdy, Sam.
我在做梦
I'm dreaming.
你看我们
What do you say…
去散个步怎么样？
you and I take a little walk?
你很安静 萨姆
You're awfully quiet, Sam.
你没跟我生气 对吧？
You're not mad at me, are you?
我会把你碎尸万段的 我发誓
I'm gonna tear you to shreds, I swear.
等你醒过来 老虎 你再全力以赴吧
When you wake up, tiger, you give it your best shot.
- 我哥在哪儿 - 别再担心迪恩了
- Where's my brother? - Quit worrying about Dean.
我是你的话会更担心自己
I'd worry more about yourself.
怎么 你要杀了我？
What, you gonna kill me?
我在帮你 这就是为什么我们在谈话
I'm trying to help you. That's why we're talking.
你是那个我一直支持的孩子
You're the one I'm rooting for.
这算什么意思？
What's that supposed to mean?
欢迎来到美国小姐竞选
Welcome to the Miss America Pageant.
你以为你在这儿是为了什么？这是一场竞赛
Why do you think you're here? This is a competition.
你们这群疯狂的孩子里 只有一个能活着离开
Only one of you crazy kids is gonna make it out of here alive.
- 我以为我们应该是 - 即将来临的战争中的战士 没错
- I thought we were supposed to be…Soldiers in a coming war? That's true.
你是 但是重点是
You are. But here's the thing.
我不需要战士
I don't need soldiers.
我需要「战士」
I need soldier.
我只需要一个
I just need the one.
- 为什么 - 我不能就这么说出来 不是吗 萨姆？
- Why? - Well, I couldn't just say that, could I Sam?
我得让每个人都认为 他们有战斗的资格
I had to let everyone think they had a fighting chance.
但是我需要的…
But what I need…
是一个领导者
is a leader.
领导谁？
To lead who?
哦 我已经有了我的军队
Oh, I've already got my army.
或者我
Or, I will…
很快就会有了 不管怎样
soon anyway.
你这狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
老实说 我很惊讶你居然没猜到
Honestly, I'm surprised you hadn't guessed.
我的意思是 你认为那么多孩子 都死了是为什么？
I mean, why do you think so many children flamed out already?
马克思·米勒还有安迪的兄弟 他的名字是什么来着？
Max Miller and Andy's brother, what's-his-name?
他们不够强
They weren't strong enough.
我在寻找你们这一代中
I'm looking for the best and brightest…
最好最聪明的
of your generation.
我这一代？
My generation?
还有其他年代的 但是让我们先考虑你这一代的
Well.There's other generations. But let's just worry about yours.
那就是为什么我在这儿 我想让你处于一个 有利的位置
That's why I'm here, Sam. I wanna give you the inside track.
你坚强 你聪明 你接受了很好的培训
You're tough, you're smart, you're well-trained.
感谢你父亲
Thanks to your daddy.
萨姆
Sam.
萨姆…
Sammy.
你是我的最爱
You're my favorite.
你毁了我的生活
You ruined my life.
你杀了每一个我爱的人
You killed everyone I love.
恐怕这就是做生意的成本
The cost of doing business, I'm afraid.
我的意思是
I mean…
甜美的小杰西卡…
sweet little Jessica?
她只是不得不死
She just had to die.
你已经准备好要和她结婚了 那个金发的小东西
You were all set to marry that little blond thing.
成为一个税务律师 两个孩子 啤酒肚 然后在市郊有一座宅邸
Become a tax lawyer with two kids, a beer gut and a McMansion in the suburbs.
我需要你变得敏锐 在路上 磨练你的技能
I needed you sharp, on the road, honing your skills…
你的天赋
your gifts.
那我的妈妈呢？
What about my mom?
- 那是坏运气 - 坏运气
- That was bad luck. - Bad luck?
她走进来看到我们 错的地点 错的时间
She walked in on us. Wrong place, wrong time.
- 这是什么意思 - 不是关于她 是关于你
- What does that mean? - It wasn't about her. It was about you.
一直都是关于你
It's always been about you.
什么？
What?
好吧…
Well.
你正好碰到了
Okay. You caught me…
我仁慈的时候
in a charitable mood.
我给你看
I'll show you.
看上去熟悉吗 应该是的
Look familiar? It should.
放松 萨姆 这只是个高真的即时回放 欣赏表演吧
Relax, Sam. This is just a hi-def instant replay. Enjoy the show.
- 约翰 - 妈妈
- John. - Mom.
他饿了吗
Is he hungry?
嘘
Shh.
- 好吧 - 妈妈
- Okay. - Mom.
妈妈
Mom.
我刚刚跟你说什么了 萨姆 她听不到你的
What did I just tell you, Sam, she can't hear you.
这不是真的
This isn't real.
- 见鬼的你在对我做什么 - 比母亲的乳汁更好
- What the hell are you doing to me? - Better than mother's milk.
这是不是意味着…
Does this mean I have…
我身体里流着恶魔的血？
demon blood in me?
回答我
Answer me.
- 是你 - 她认识你
- It's you. - She knew you.
不
No.
我想你不会想看剩下的
I don't think you wanna see the rest of this.
萨姆 醒醒
Sam. Wake up.
艾娃不见了
Ava's missing.
我去检查畜舍和旅馆 你去检查房子
I'll take the barn and the hotel, you take the houses.
好的 10分钟后回来这儿见 好吗？
All right. Meet back here in 10 minutes, okay?
好的
Okay.
艾娃
Ava.
你跑哪儿去了？
Where'd you go?
- 你没听到我们喊你吗 - 是的 我有听到你
- Didn't you hear us yelling? - Yeah, I heard you.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
天啊…
Holy.
萨姆 我找到他时 他就这样了
Sam. I just found him like this.
- 发生什么事了 - 我不知道
- What happened? - I don't know.
那东西怎么进来的？
How'd that thing get in?
你刚才在哪儿？
Where were you?
我只是去井里弄点水
I just went to get some water from the well.
我只走开了大概2分钟
I was only gone maybe, like, two minutes.
你不应该出去的 艾娃我们必须待在房子里
You shouldn't have gone outside. Ava, we have to stay in here.
那是谁干的？
Who did that?
- 我不知道 也许是安迪… - 安迪不会这么做的
- I don't know, maybe Andy…Andy wouldn't do that.
艾娃 我走的时候 盐线还没有断
Ava, that line wasn't broken when I left.
- 艾娃 - 什么 你不会认为…
- Ava. - Why? You don't think that I-
我来告诉你我怎么想的 5个月了…
I'll tell you what I think. Five months.
你是唯一一个不能说明 那段时间自己在哪儿的人
You're the only one with all that time you can't account for.
你头疼的时候
And that headache you got.
- 正是莉莉被劫走的时候 - 你想要说什么？
- Right when the demon got Lily. - What are you trying to say?
- 你到底怎么了 - 什么也没有
- What happened to you? - Nothing.
最终还是没骗倒你 是吗？
I had you going though, didn't I?
是啊
Yeah.
我来这里已经很久了 也并不孤单… 不断有人出现
I've been here a long time. And not alone, either. People just keep showing up.
孩子们 像我们这样的…
Children, like us.
一批大概3或4个人
Batches of three or four at a time.
你杀了他们 全部？
You killed them? All of them?
我是这里不可战胜的 重量级冠军
I'm the undefeated heavyweight champ.
哦 我的上帝啊
Oh, my God.
我想上帝没什么用处 萨姆
Don't think God has much to do with this, Sam.
你怎么能？
How could you?
我没有选择
I had no choice.
不是我死就是他们亡 过了一段时间 也挺容易的
It was me or them. After a while, it was easy.
甚至也很有趣
It was even kind of fun.
- 我只是不再斗争了 - 斗争什么？
- I just stopped fighting it. - Fighting what?
我们是谁 萨姆
Who we are, Sam.
如果你挣脱自己的束缚 张开双臂
If you just quit your hand-wringing and open yourself up…
你根本不知道自己的能耐
you have no idea what you can do.
学习过程非常快 近乎颠狂 那开关 就像在你脑子里一样
The learning curve is so fast, it's crazy. The switches that just flip in your brain.
真不敢相信我是从 做梦开始的
I can't believe I started out just having dreams.
你知道我现在能做什么吗？
Do you know what I can do now?
控制魔鬼
Control demons.
你也很快
You are quick on the draw.
很抱歉 萨姆
I'm sorry, Sam…
但是… 都结束了
but it's over.
看来剩下的路要步行了
It looks like the rest of the way's on foot.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我- 想现在我们能离开这里了 - 但那个阿奇雷魔鬼…
- I think we can make it out of here now. - But the Acheri demon-
不 不 不 是艾娃召唤控制的
No, no. Ava was summoning it, controlling it.
她死了那东西就不会出来了 我们得离开了
It shouldn't come back now that she's dead. We gotta go.
不是「我们」 萨姆
Not we, Sam.
我们之中只有一个能离开这里 我很抱歉
Only one of us is getting out of here. I'm sorry.
- 什么 - 我… 我有过幻象
- What? - I…I had a vision.
那个黄眼魔鬼 不管他是什么… 他和我说过话 他告诉我怎么回事
That Yellow-Eyed demon or whatever. He talked to me. He told me how it was.
- 不 扎克 听着 你不能相信他的话 - 萨姆 他不会让我们走的
- Oh, no Jake, you can't listen to him…Sam, he's not letting us go.
只有一个人
Only one.
我们不单飞的话 他会把我们两个都杀死
Now, we don't play along, he'll kill us both.
我喜欢你 老兄 真的
Now, I like you, man, I do.
但你仔细想想 我们两个都死了有什么好处？
But do the math here. What good's it do for both of us to die?
我能离开这里 我接近那魔鬼
Now, I can get out of here. I get close to the demon.
- 我能杀了那杂种 - 和我一起 我们可以一起杀了他
- I can kill the bastard. - You come with me, we kill him together.
- 我怎么知道你不会出卖我 - 我不会的
- How do I know you won't turn on me? - I won't.
我可不确定
I don't know that.
好吧 瞧
Okay. Look.
和我一起去吧 扎克
Just come with me, Jake.
别这样
Don't do this.
别让他得到他想要的
Don't play into what it wants.
好吧
Okay.
萨姆
Sam!
- 萨姆 - 迪恩
- Sam. - Dean.
萨姆 小心
Sam. Look out.
不
No.
萨姆
Sam.
萨姆 萨姆
Sam. Sam.
萨姆 嘿
Sam. Hey.
来这边 让我看看你
Hey, come here. You're okay, champ.
你瞧 看着我 没那么糟
Hey. Look. Look at me. It's not even that bad.
没那么糟 好吗
It's not even that bad, right?
萨姆？萨姆 嘿 听我说 我们会把你治好的 好吗？
Sammy? Sam. Hey, listen to me. We're gonna patch you up, okay?
你会完好痊愈的
You'll be good as new. Huh?
我会照顾你的
I'm gonna take care of you.
我照顾你 这是我的责任 对吗？
I got you. It's my job, right?
看着我那没出息的弟弟
Watch out for my pain-in-the-ass little brother.
萨姆？
Sam.
萨姆 萨姆
Sam. Sam.
萨姆
Sammy.
不 不 不 不
No. No, no, no.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
萨姆
Sam!